太好了  再见
Okay, great. Bye.
猜猜谁要来吃感恩节晚餐
So guess who's coming to Thanksgiving dinner.
薛尼鲍迪
Sidney Poitier? Ha, ha.
我怀念瑞秋
I miss Rachel.
不  是我爸妈
No, my parents.
太好了  我搬进来之后  他们还没来过
Oh, That’s great, they haven't seen the place since I moved in.
对  要是你能不提同居的事  就太好了
Yeah, and y'know, if you could not mention that we live together, that'd be great.
我打算四点左右开动
I was thinking we'd eat around 4.
为什么不能提同居的事
Why can't I tell them we live together?
因为他们不知道我们在交往  要在厨房吃吗
Because they don't know we're dating. Do you think we should eat in the kitchen?
你为什么没有告诉他们
Why haven't you told them?
我本来要说  真的
Um, well, I was going to. I really was.
但是后来不知怎的  就没说了
But, urn, then somewhere, just out of nowhere, I didn't.
你为什么没说   他们会不开心吗
Why haven't you told them? Wouldn't they be happy?
四点左右厨房开动   到时候见
So, dinner in the kitchen around 4. I'll see you then.
他们为什么会不开心
Why wouldn't they be happy?
因为
Well, um, because...
主要是
...mainly, um...
他们不喜欢你
...they don't like you.
对不起  什么   为什么
I'm sorry. What? Why? Why?
也许是因为你以前很冷漠
Maybe because you used to be aloof...
很尖酸刻薄   老爱开玩笑
...or that you're really sarcastic or that you joke around all the time...
或许是因为你脱了衣服喜欢乱丢
...or that you take off your clothes and throw them on the couch.
这是他们的还是你的看法
Is this why they don't like me or why you don't like me?
我知道我应该告诉他们  我不该在意他们
I know I should have told them. I know I shouldn't care what they think.
对不起
I'm sorry.
其实没关系   等他们来了  我会表现得很迷人
You know, it'll be okay, because when they come over, I will be charming.
我会让他们爱上我   然后我们再说
I will make them love me, then we'll tell them.
你真的觉得可行
You really think that'll work?
我也可以很有魅力  我不就赢得了你的心
Hey, I can be pretty charming, babe. I won you over, didn't I?
你应该不会把他们灌得那么醉吧
I don't think you'll ever get my parents that drunk.
老友记  第六季  第9集  感恩的季节
Friends  S06E09  The One Where Ross Got High
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
嘿  太好了  罗斯  你爸妈喜欢我  对吧
Hey. Oh, good, Ross. Your parents like me, right?
他们当然喜欢你
Yes, of course they like you.
摩妮卡说他们不喜欢我
Monica told me they don't.
对  他们不喜欢你
Yeah, they don't like you.
你知道原因吗
Do you know why?
也许是因为你很尖酸刻薄  或者是因为
Maybe it's because you're really sarcastic, or maybe it's because you--
不知道就不要乱猜
If people don't know, they shouldn't just guess.
帅啊  又一个不值得感恩的感恩节
This is great, Another Thanksgiving with nothing to give thanks for.
也许我可以感恩你闭嘴
Maybe I could give thanks for you shutting up, huh?
也许我也可以感恩  你把我的电动送到我的新家
Maybe I give thanks by taking my PlayStation to my new apartment.
也许我爱你
Maybe I love you.
嗨  嗨
Hi. Hi.
你们好
Hey, guys.
不要  我不想打电动  乔伊
No, I don't want to play video games, Joey.
你们要去钱德家过感恩节吗
Are you guys going to Chandler's for Thanksgiving?
对  怎么了
Yeah, why, what's up?
我和几个舞者朋友想一起庆祝
Well, me and my dancer friends are thinking of doing Thanksgiving uptown.
我想说你们可能想去
I thought you guys might like to come.
真的去
For real?
你们是该去钱德家  我们没有人会做菜
No, but you should go to Chandler's. Because none of us knows how to cook,
最后八成都在喝酒
We'll probably just drink all day.
我们去  好
We go to yours. Yeah.
对  我们得过去露个面  毕竟她是我妹妹
Yeah, see, we have to stop across the hall because it's my sister.
不过有个妹妹是好事啊
But, you know, actually, uh, growing up with a sister was nice...
让我很了解女人心
...because it really helped me understand women.
你应该告诉你的朋友们
Yeah, you should tell your friends that.
好
0Kay.
真不知道你怎么能骗到三个老婆
How you got three women to marry you, I'll never know.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
菲比  你看  感恩节甜点
Pheebs, check it out. For my dessert...
我决定做酒果酱松糕
...I have chosen to make a traditional English trifle.
听起来好棒   摩妮卡你的呢
Wow, that sounds great. And what are you making, Monica?
万一瑞秋的甜点  好吃的被我吃光光
In case Rachel's dessert is so good that I eat all of it...
别人会没有吃的了
...and there's none left for anybody else.
我不做
Nothing.
你不做
Nothing?
对  我信任你
No, sweetie. I trust you.
所以要是我搞砸了  就没有甜点了
So if I mess this up, there's nothing else for dessert?
你不会搞砸的
You're not gonna mess it up.
摩妮卡  我好高兴  你真的对我有信心  谢谢
Wow, Monica, I love that. You really have faith in me. Thank you.
技术问题  这些奶油什么时候好
Technical question: How do you know when the butter is done?
两分钟前  大约变成这样
Well, it's done about two minutes before it looks like that.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
菜闻起来好香  这里布置得真漂亮
Oh. The food smells great, Mon. And the place looks so nice.
感恩节快乐  感恩节快乐
Hey, happy Thanksgiving, everybody. Happy Thanksgiving.
感恩节快乐
Happy Thanksgiving.
真是开心  再见
Well, this has been great. See you.
你们要去哪里
Where you going? Oh, oh.
我们说过  要去参加乔伊的室友的聚会
We did say we'd stop by this little thing Joey's roommate is having.
火辣舞者吉宁
Oh, Janine, the really hot dancer girl?
有些人会说她很有魅力
Some would say she's attractive, yes.
还有谁会去
Who else is going to be there?
她的几个朋友   全是舞者朋友
Uh, some of her friends. Her dancer friends?
对啦  好不好
Yes. All right?
她的性感舞者朋友都会去的
All of her hot dancer friends are gonna be there...
她们会喝酒跳舞  我们真的很想去
...and they'll be drinking and dancing and we really want to go.
都快成功了
Dude, we were good.
你们哪儿也不准去  你们说要来吃饭就别想跑
You're not gonna go anywhere, You said you'd eat here and you'll eat here.
扔下我们去看性感舞者
Yeah, and leaving us to go see hot dancer girls...
就是不太感恩的
...is not very Thanksgiving-y.
但是
Oh, but it is.
第一个感恩节就是这样  印地安人和清教徒共进晚餐
Uh, it's like the first Thanksgiving when the Indians and Pilgrims sat down.
对  然后印地安人告诉清教徒
Yeah, and then the Indians taught the Pilgrims...
新世界的性感定义是什么
...what it meant to be hot in the New World.
大家好  嗨
Hello, everybody. Hi.
爸  妈
Hi, Dad. Morn.
看  这谁啊  钱德啊
Look. Look who it is. It's Chandler.
当然了  钱德  你好
Oh, yes, of course. Hello, Chandler.
伯父  伯母  你们的气色真好
Mr. and Mrs. Geller, you look wonderful.
欢迎  外套给我们吧
It is great to have you here. Let us take your coats.
外面在下雪吗
Whoa, it snowing out there?
没有
No.
摩妮卡  菜看起来都好棒啊
Monica, all this food looks wonderful.
你应该考虑走这一行
You should think about doing this for a living.
就算我有头皮屑  你也不必指着我笑
Okay, I have dandruff. There's no need to laugh and point.
爸  钱德是在笑你的笑话
Dad, Chandler was laughing at yourjoke.
我的笑话又不好笑
My joke wasn't funny.
瑞秋  我刚刚想到
Rach, I just remembered.
我昨晚梦到盖勒先生
I had a dream about Mr. Geller last night.
真的吗
Really?
对  我梦到他把我从火场救出
Yeah. I dreamt that he saved me from a burning building...
他好英勇好强壮
...and he was so brave and so strong.
我对他完全改变了看法
And it's making me look at him totally differently.
他以前只是 "杰克盖勒  摩妮卡和罗斯的爸爸"
You know, I mean, he used to be just "Jack Geller, Monica and Ross' dad."
现在他是 "杰克盖勒  梦中情人"
Now he's "Jack Geller, dream hunk."
不知道  对我来说他永远都是杰克盖勒
I don't know. To me, he'll always be "Jack Geller...
在你换衣服时闯进来
...walks in while you're changing."
爸  钱德是罗斯最要好的朋友之一
You know, Dad, Chandler is one of Ross' very best friends.
罗斯是个好青年
Ross sure is a great guy.
我一直觉得儿子
You know, I've always felt that how a young man turns out...
是父亲的翻版
...is a reflection on his father.
我也有同感   请问你爸是做什么的
I always thought that too. Tell me, what does your father do?
他是同志歌舞秀
He's a headliner of a...
的头牌
...gay burlesque show.
瑞秋  你急死人了  快上甜点啦
Rash, you're killing us. Will you serve the dessert already?
酒醉的舞者都在等我们
There's drunken dancers a-waiting.
你们看  很漂亮吧
Look at it. Isn't it beautiful?
是啊  这是什么
Yeah. What is it?
酒果酱松糕  有很多层
It's a trifle. It's got all these layers.
先是一层小松糕   然后是果酱
First there's a layer of ladyfingers, then a layer of jam...
然后是我自己做的乳蛋糕
...then custard, which I made from scratch...
然后是覆盖盆子  然后又是小松糕
...then raspberries, more ladyfingers...
然后是豌豆洋葱炒嫩牛肉
...then beef sauteed with peas and onions...
然后又有一点乳蛋糕
...then a little bit more custard...
然后是香蕉   最后再涂上鲜奶油
...then bananas and then I put whipped cream on top.
香蕉前面是什么
What was the one right before bananas?
炒牛肉吗  我也觉得有点奇怪
The beef. Yeah, that was weird to me too.
不过我想说  "连甜肉馅饼都有了"
But then, y'know, I thought, "Well, there's minced meat pie."
那是一种英式甜点
That's an English dessert.
英国人都放一堆怪东西
These people just put very strange things in their food.
对了  可以跟你借兰姆酒吗
By the way, can I borrow rum from your place?
当然可以
Yeah, sure.
我不在的时候你们可别偷吃
And while I'm gone, don't you boys sneak a taste.
好  好
okay. okay
甜点加牛肉
Beef in a dessert?
不  不  不可能的
No, no, no. There is no way.
就是啊  而且果酱才一层
I know. And only one layer of jam?
有没有搞错
What is up with that?
天哪  这
Oh, my God.
两页黏在一起了  钱德
The pages are stuck together. Chandler.
天哪  她做了酒果酱松糕加
Oh, my God. She made half an English trifle and...
肉馅马铃薯泥饼
...half a shepherd's pie.
完了  她得重做了
Man, now she's gonna start all over.
我们没办法带那些辣妹  认识新世界了
We're never gonna get to introduce the hot girls to the New World.
不  我们可以  不要告诉她就是了
No, no, we will. We just won't tell her she messed up.
然后让她上那个牛肉乳蛋糕
Just let her serve the beef-custard thing?
对  这会是一个有趣的感恩节回忆
Yeah. It'll be like a funny Thanksgiving story.
呕吐的回忆  的确很有趣
Vomiting stories are funny, I guess.
乔伊  天哪  你家热死了
Joey. God, your apartment is like a hundred degrees.
你会不会想脱到只剩下内衣
Did it make you want to walk around in your underwear?
不会
No.
还不够热
Still not hot enough.
瑞秋  怎样  你看他
Rachel. Okay, look at him.
你看那双有力的手
Look at those strong hands.
我真想当那瓶…炼乳
Oh, what I wouldn't give to be that can of condensed milk.
妈  钱德说你的毛衣很好看
Mom, uh, Chandler was just saying how beautiful your sweater is.
谢谢你  这是新衣服
Oh, thank you, Chandler. I just bought it.
是吗  很漂亮  米色的  很紧
Oh. Yes, well, it's very beautiful and it's cream-colored and tight and...
我不是指很紧  不会很紧  我没有在看
I don't mean tight. It's not too tight. Not that I was looking at...
他是怎么搞的
What's the matter with him?
大概又嗑药了
I think he's stoned again.
什么  什么
What? What?
我有事要告诉你
Dude, I need to talk to you a sec.
我大概知道  我爸妈为什么不喜欢你了
Okay, I think I might know why my parents don't like you.
是吗  为什么  记不记得我们年轻的时候
You do? Why? Okay, remember we were young. Heh.
大二的春假  我在房间里吸麻
Spring break, sophomore year, I got high in my bedroom...
我爸妈走进来闻到了
...and my parents walked in and smelled it...
于是我就说你吸了麻   跳窗走了
...so I told them that you had gotten stoned and jumped out the window.
什么  你为什么要赖给我
What? Why did you do that?
我不知道  我第一个想到你
I don't know. Uh, yours was the first name that popped into my head.
对不起  我以为不会怎样
I'm sorry. I didn't think it'd matter.
怎么可能不会怎样
How could it not matter?
我怎么知道我们会变成死党
How was I to know we'd be friends after college...
更别提你会跟我妹同居
...let alone you'd be living with my sister?
那些 "生死之交"的豪语呢
What about all that "friends forever" stuff?
不晓得  我当时正嗨
I don't know. I was all high.
爸妈叫我来看看  你是不是想找罗斯嗑药
Mom and Dad just sent me to find out if you were trying to get Ross stoned.
罗斯大学吸麻被他们逮到  他居然赖给我
Your parents caught Ross smoking pot in college, and he blamed it on me.
罗斯  你怎么能这样
Ross, I can't believe you'd do that.
他们讨厌我  我们才没公开  麻烦你搞定
We haven't told them we're together because they hate me, okay? So you fix this.
好啦  我会说吸麻的不是钱德
Okay, okay, I'll tell them it wasn't Chandler who got high.
那我要说是谁呢
Now, who should I say it was?
你  这又没什么  你现在又没有嗑药
You. It's not like it's a big deal. You don't still do it or anything.
好啦  好啦  那我要说是谁骗我这么做的
All right. Now, who should I say tricked me into doing it?
爸
Dad.
请别在这里剔牙
Dad, please don't pick your teeth out here.
如果你要翘脚  怎么不坐   摩妮卡  不要烦他
And if you're gonna put your feet up-Monica, leave him alone.
你快点  好吗
Will you hurry up?
你之前没听到我说  吉宁的朋友都是舞者吗
Did you not hear me when I told you that all of Janine's friends are dancers?
而且她们会喝很多酒
Huh? And that they're gonna be drinking a lot?
我是听到了  不过你再说一次  好浪漫
No, I did. But tell me again because it's so romantic.
你打得好慢  不能快一点吗
You're whipping so slow. Can't you do it any faster?
乔伊  我不想犯错
Joey, come on, I don't want to make any mistakes.
甜点只有这一道   要是我搞砸   大家会说
This is the only dessert. If I screw it up, everybody's gonna be like:
"记得那次感恩节  瑞秋把酒果酱松糕做坏了"
"Oh, remember that Thanksgiving when Rachel screwed up the trifle?"
所以让我来做  你只管担心吃的部分
So just let me worry about making the trifle and you just worry about eating it.alright?
我是很担心
Oh, I am.
罗斯  你再不说  我就要说了  好啦
Ross, if you don't tell them, then I will. Okay. Fine.
罗斯  你可以来一下吗
Ross, can I talk to you for a second? Oh, uh...
等一下好吗   乔伊  我有事要告诉我爸吗
Can it wait a second, Joey? I have to tell my parents something.
不能等  好吧
No, it can't? Okay.
我觉得我们应该告诉瑞秋  她甜点做错了
Okay, look, I think we have to tell Rachel she messed up her dessert.
什么  大家都是怎么了
What? What is with everybody?
今天是感恩节  不是
It's Thanksgiving, not...
告秘日
...Truth Day.
等大家吃到那道香蕉肉甜点
Look, when everyone eats that banana-meat thing...
一定会取笑她  那样的话也好吗
...they'll all make fun of her. Do you want that?
好  我们就叫大家假装喜欢
Okay. We'll just get everyone to act like they like it.
那样就不会有人取笑她
That way, no one makes fun of her...
我们也可以去找那些小辣椒
...and we still get to go to sweet potato pie.
兄弟  别把她们物化
Dude, they're not objects.
好
Oh.
开玩笑的  我去告诉大家  你把瑞秋拖开
Just kidding. I'll talk to them. You distract her.
瑞秋  可以出去谈一下吗
Hey, Rach, can I talk to you outside for a sec'?
好吧
0Kay.
什么事  罗斯
What's up, Ross?
所以
So, um...
感恩节
Thanksgiving.
岁末季节又来了
The holiday season is upon us, hmm?
是啊
Yeah.
还有
And, um...
你今天很漂亮
...you look nice today.
不  不  罗斯  不要这样  什么
Oh, no. No, Ross, don't do this. What?
我觉得我们不适合复合了
I just don't think us getting back together is a good idea.
嗯
Huh?
我早就料到会这样
I thought this might happen today.
罗斯  我知道逢年过节特别难熬
Ross, I know the holidays can be rough...
而且你一个人八成很辛苦
...and it's probably really hard for you to be alone right now.
你也是一个人
You're alone.
不  我跟菲比住
No, I live with Phoebe.
你就真的只有一个人
I mean, you're alone-alone.
好吗  但这个时机真的不对   抱歉
And it's just not the time for us. I'm sorry.
我总得试试看
Oh, well. Can't blame a guy for trying.
要是有人不知道怎么装
And, uh, if anyone needs help pretending to like it...
我在表演课学过  你们可以摸摸肚子
...I learned some things in acting class. Try, uh, rubbing your stomach.
或是说 "嗯"
Or, uh, saying "Mm."
加上微笑
And, uh, oh, smiling.
好啊
Okay?
我再也不花钱  让你去上表演课了
Yeah, I'm not gonna pay for those acting classes anymore.
瑞秋  你回来了  快上甜点吧
Rachel, there you are. Come on, Let's serve that dessert already.
乔伊   别再催我了  你知道吗   罚你不准吃
Joey, you have to stop rushing me. You know what? You don't get any dessert.
是么
Really?
骗你的  我才不会虐待你
No, just kidding. I would never do that to you.
好  各位  酒果酱松糕时间到
Okay, everybody, it's trifle time.
这是英式酒果酱松糕  对吧
So, now, Rach, this is a traditional English trifle, isn't it?
一点也没错
It sure is. Wow.
那你是加牛肉还是茄子
So did you make it with beef or eggplant?
牛肉  我不能吃  你也知道我不吃肉
Beet I can't have any. I don't eat meat. Oh.
哦
Aw.
摩妮卡  我要你第一个品尝
Monica, I want you to have the first taste.
是吗
Really?
等等  你只挖了鲜奶油
Wait, you only got whipped cream.
你得挖到每一层
You gotta take a bite with all the layers.
好
0Kay.
等等  你掉了一颗豌豆
You dropped a pea.
怎么样
Well?
嗯
Mm.
好好吃
It's good.
真的吗  多好吃
Really? How good?
好吃到
It's so good that I feel really selfish...
我一个人吃会过意不去
...about being the only one who's eating it.
我们应该让每个人都享用
I think we should have everyone taste how good it is.
尤其是罗斯
Especially Ross.
真是太好吃了  我要去阳台吃
Yeah. This is so good that I'm gonna go enjoy it on the balcony.
边看风景边享用
So that I can enjoy the view whilst I enjoy my dessert.
我要去房里打电话
I've gotta call my friend...
告诉我的朋友玛丽有多好吃
...and tell her how good this is from Monica's room.
我帮你拨号
I'll help you dial.
我要去浴室
I'm gonna go into the bathroom...
边吃边照镜子
...so I can look at it in the mirror as I eat it.
这是怎么回事  不好吃吗
Okay, what was that all about? Does it not taste good?
我吃吃看  什么  不行
Let me try it. No, no.
都没了
All gone.
好好吃
So good.
也许钱德还有剩的
Maybe Chandler has some left.
味道好像洗脚水
It tastes like feet.
我喜欢
I like it.
不是吧
Are you kidding?
有什么不好  乳蛋糕  赞
What's not to like? Custard, good.
果酱  赞  牛肉  赞
Jam, good. Meat, good.
一只乌就这样一把抢过去
So a bird just grabbed it...
想带着它飞走
...and then tried to fly away with it...
结果就掉到马路上了
...and then just dropped it on the street?
对  不过值得安慰的是  掉下去之前
Yes, but, if it's any consolation, before the bird dropped it...
他好像吃得很开心
...he seemed to enjoy it.
瑞秋  来一下
Rachel, come here.
好
0Kay.
我刚刚小睡了一觉  又梦到杰克
I was just taking my Thanksgiving nap and I had another dream about Jack.
菲比  我会想听吗  我不知道  你听听看
Phoebe, do I want to hear this? I don't know, let's see.
所以  我梦到我们正要结婚
Okay, I dreamt we were getting married...
结果他离开去救火
...and he left because he had to go fight a fire.
所以我去一家夜总会  却看到他在跟一个女孩亲热
And, um, so, okay, I went to a nightclub and I saw him making outwith a girl.
天哪  他在梦里背叛你
Oh, my God, he dream-cheated on you.
对  但这时贾克库斯托出现
Yeah. But then Jacques Cousteau came...
帮我教训了他一顿
...and he kicked his ass for betraying me.
好酷喔
It was so cool.
然后他带我去潜水  跟我介绍他养的海马
Then he took me diving and introduced me to his pet sea horse...
他一直对我献殷勤  但是怎么可能
...who was coming on to me. And, please, that is not gonna happen.
幸好我今天系了大皮带
Boy, I'm glad I wore the big belt today.
五分钟前  那种话会让我神魂颠倒
Five minutes ago, a line like that would have floored me.
现在却毫无作用   一点点啦  我毕竟是女人
But now, nothing. Well, not nothing. I am still a woman.
罗斯  来吧
Ross? Let's go.
关于告诉爸妈这件事
Oh, yeah. About telling Mom and Dad...
我考虑用写信的方式
...I was thinking about maybe writing a letter.
够了  我给过你机会
You know what? That's it. You've had your chance.
妈  爸  罗斯大学吸过麻
Mom, Dad. Ross smoked pot in college.
什么  什么
What? What?
你这个告密者
You are such a tattletale.
妈  爸
Mom, Dad, heh...
记得你们在我房里
...you remember that time you walked in my room...
闻到大麻的事吗
...and smelled marijuana?
记得 记得
Yes. Yes.
我说吸麻的是钱德
I told you it was Chandler...
其实
...who was smoking the pot but...
是我  对不起
...it was me. I'm sorry.
是你
It was you?
还有  害他被革职的邮差
And, Dad, you know that mailman that you got fired?
他没有偷你的《花花公子》   是罗斯偷的
He didn't steal your Playboys. Ross did.
前廊的秋千椅不是暴风雨弄坏的  是摩妮卡坐坏的
Well, Hurricane Gloria didn't break the porch swing. Monica did.
罗斯已经离开博物馆一年了
Ross hasn't worked at the museum for a year.
摩妮卡和钱德在同居
Monica and Chandler are living together!
罗斯在赌城娶了瑞秋  然后又离婚了  又一次
Ross married Rachel in Vegas. And got divorced. Again!
我爱贾克库斯托
I love Jacques Cousteau.
酒果酱松糕里不该放牛肉的
I wasn't supposed to put beef in the trifle.
我想走啦
I want to go!
这三十秒真是高潮不断啊
That's a lot of information to get in 3O seconds.
好  乔伊  你想走就走吧
All right. Joey, if you want to leave, just leave.
瑞秋  这道甜点的确不能放肉
Rachel, no, you weren't supposed to put beef in the trifle.
一点也不好吃
It did not taste good.
菲比  很抱歉
Phoebe, I'm sorry...
贾克库斯托已经死了
...but I think Jacques Cousteau is dead.
摩妮卡  我真不懂  你为何
Monica, why you felt you had to hide the fact...
要隐瞒一段重要的感情
...that you're in an important relationship is beyond me.
其实秋千椅的事我们心里有数
And we kind of figured about the porch swing.
罗斯
Ross.
嗑药
Drugs?
三度离婚
Divorced again?
你是怎么了  儿子
What happened, son?
我都是遭人哄骗
L-I, uh-I got tricked into all those things.
钱德  你一直是罗斯的好朋友
Chandler, you've been Ross' best friend all these years...
在他嗑药时仍不放弃他
...stuck by him during the drug problems...
现在你又照顾起摩妮卡
...and now you've taken on Monica as well.
我不知道该说什么
Well, I don't know what to say.
你真是个大好人
You're a wonderful human being.
谢谢你  不
Thank you. No.
是谢谢你
Thank you.
摩妮卡  罗斯  我真不知道该拿你们怎么办
Monica and Ross, I don't know what I'm gonna do about the two of you.
我会跟他们谈
I'll talk to them.
各位  香蕉
You guys, it was bananas...
奶油加牛肉
...cream and beef.
你们居然因为怕我难过而吃掉
I just cannot believe that you ate that so that I wouldn't feel bad.
其实我没吃  还放在浴室里
Well, actually, I didn't eat mine. It's still in the bathroom.
没有  我吃掉了
No it isn't, I ate that.
我们的在摩妮卡的房里
And we left ours in Monica's bedroom.
没有  被我吃了  你的也是
Nope, got it and got yours too.